import { Question } from "../App";

export const friendsData: Question[] =
    [
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Ross's first wife?",
            "options": ["Carol", "Rachel", "Emily", "Susan"],
            "answer": "Carol"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Chandler Bing's middle name?",
            "options": ["Muriel", "Matthew", "Michael", "Marcel"],
            "answer": "Muriel"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the coffee shop where the friends frequently hang out?",
            "options": ["Central Perk", "Monk's Café", "Java Joe's", "The Beanery"],
            "answer": "Central Perk"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which character famously said, 'We were on a break!'?",
            "options": ["Ross", "Rachel", "Chandler", "Joey"],
            "answer": "Ross"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Joey's stuffed penguin?",
            "options": ["Hugsy", "Waddle", "Flipper", "Snowball"],
            "answer": "Hugsy"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the profession of Ross Geller?",
            "options": ["Paleontologist", "Chef", "Actor", "Data Analyst"],
            "answer": "Paleontologist"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Monica’s first kiss?",
            "options": ["Ross", "Chandler", "Joey", "Richard"],
            "answer": "Ross"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Phoebe’s most famous song?",
            "options": ["Smelly Cat", "Sticky Shoes", "Terrible Mistress", "Little Black Curly Hair"],
            "answer": "Smelly Cat"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which character has a twin sister named Ursula?",
            "options": ["Phoebe", "Monica", "Rachel", "Janice"],
            "answer": "Phoebe"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the holiday armadillo?",
            "options": ["Ross", "Chandler", "Joey", "Monica"],
            "answer": "Ross"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the names of Monica and Chandler’s twins?",
            "options": ["Erica and Jack", "Ben and Emma", "Frank Jr. Jr. and Leslie", "Michael and Amanda"],
            "answer": "Erica and Jack"
        }
    ]
    ;